KERRY: I really love my job and what I do,
and getting to see them develop and grow
as young people and support their families
to have the best quality for these
young people is the best part of my job.
And during the first lockdown, there
was a family struggling because their
usual community access wasn't there.
Residential was shut down.
It wasn't safe for this young
person to be in school because
they have other medical needs.
And what we did was arrange for
us to take one of the school cars
and go and take him for a drive
once a week, just for half an hour.
He loved it because he loves roads and
maps and he was giving me directions
the entire time, finding it hilarious
to drive me down dead ends and then
have me reverse out thinking it was
great and I'm there and there's a
big bus going, "oh my goodness, how
am I going to fit down this road?".
But it gave his family a chance to sit
down and have a cup of tea or, you know,
get the washing done or spend some time
with his siblings and that, but how
much he loved seeing us again, after
quite a gap and how much he enjoyed
that time away from home as well doing
something he enjoyed was really lovely.
In a mainstream setting when I used to
work in a year three class and there
was a young boy in there with autism,
we worked, this was before I had an
awful lot of knowledge of autism I will
admit, we worked really hard on getting
him to communicate to us when he needed
help, because he would just sit lost
in a sea of about 35 children and just
just wait for you to come around to him.
And the first day he picked up his
help card and held it in the air was
just, oh, it was an amazing moment.
It was really good, so to see him
come on and his communication and
how he's doing was was fantastic.